<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" ?>
<languages>
  <language name="English" id="EN">
    <bvnetwork>
      <sendmail>
        <enum>
          <recipientlisttype>
            <privatelist>Recipient List</privatelist>
            <blocklist>BlockList</blocklist>
            <publiclist>Public List</publiclist>
          </recipientlisttype>
        </enum>
        <plugin>
          <newsletteradmin>
            <displayname>Administer Newsletter</displayname>
            <description>Administer your newsletters, show recipients, reports and more.</description>
          </newsletteradmin>
          <sendmail>
            <status>
              <schedulernotrunning>The Scheduler is not running!</schedulernotrunning>
              <schedulernotrunningdesc>No emails can be sent while the EPiServer Scheduler Service is stopped. Please contact your system administrator.</schedulernotrunningdesc>
            </status>
            <quickselectionlabel>Quick Selection:</quickselectionlabel>
            <previewbutton>Preview</previewbutton>
            <showallgroupsbutton>Show All Groups</showallgroupsbutton>
            <sendingtips>
              If the checkbox below is ticked, no emails will be sent to the selected recipientgroup.
              The status email will be sent with information about the sending process.
              &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
              You should always test the sending process using a testgroup with only a few recipients
              to ensure the design and sending process works as expected, before sending to a larger
              group of recipients.
            </sendingtips>
            <beforesendingwarning>
              After you have clicked the Send button, please allow the sending process to complete before you click
              any button or link. Note, the process can take some time if the group contains many recipients.
              &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
              On completion, a status will be shown, and the same information will be emailed the sender of this
              newsletter.
            </beforesendingwarning>
            <testsendercheckbox>Test and validate sending process, no emails will be sent to the recipient group</testsendercheckbox>
            <addtesttosubject>Change subject to indicate that this is a test send</addtesttosubject>
            <testpostfix>{0} (Test)</testpostfix>
            <accessWarning>Everyone does not have access to the newsletter. Usergroup everyone need read access.</accessWarning>
          </sendmail>
          <importusers>
            <displayname>Import Newsletter Users</displayname>
            <description>Import users as recipients of a specified newsletter (adding them to an EPiServer group)</description>
          </importusers>
          <commerce>
            <customer_AllContacts>All contacts</customer_AllContacts>
          </commerce>
        </plugin>
        <subscribe>
          <errornoemail>No email address provided. Please provide an email address that should be used for subscription</errornoemail>
          <commitbutton>Subscribe</commitbutton>
          <title>Subscribe to Newsletters</title>
          <email>Email Address:</email>
          <alreadysubscribe>You already subscribe to the newsletter.</alreadysubscribe>
          <admexistinguseraddtogroup>The user already exists, group membership as been updated.</admexistinguseraddtogroup>
          <admnewuser>The user {0} was created, and added to the group {1}.</admnewuser>
          <selectnewsletters>Select the newsletters you want to subscribe to:</selectnewsletters>
          <resultlabel>Subscription Result:</resultlabel>
        </subscribe>
        <unsubscribe>
          <errornoemail>No email address provided. Please provide an email address that has been used for subscription</errornoemail>
          <commitbutton>Unsubscribe</commitbutton>
          <title>Unsubscribe to Newsletters</title>
          <email>Email Address:</email>
          <selectnewsletters>Select the newsletters you would like to unsubscribe from:</selectnewsletters>
          <nosubscriptionfound>The email has not been registered for subscription on this newsletter. Please check the email address.</nosubscriptionfound>
          <nouserfound>The email cannot be found as a recipient of any newsletter in our system. Please check the address.</nouserfound>
          <recipientremoved>The email address has been unsubscribed.</recipientremoved>
          <resultlabel>Unsubscription Result:</resultlabel>
        </unsubscribe>
      </sendmail>
    </bvnetwork>
  </language>
</languages>